<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title></title>
    <link>//localhost:1313/</link>
    <description>Recent content on </description>
    <generator>Hugo</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Fri, 03 Nov 2023 00:00:00 +0800</lastBuildDate>
    <atom:link href="//localhost:1313/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>The Y-Combinator</title>
      <link>//localhost:1313/posts/2023-11-03-ycombinator/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 03 Nov 2023 00:00:00 +0800</pubDate>
      <guid>//localhost:1313/posts/2023-11-03-ycombinator/</guid>
      <description>Richard Feynman famously said &amp;ldquo;The more you teach, the better you learn&amp;rdquo;. I recently finished The Little Schemer (my review) in which I found some topics difficult to wrap my head around. So in an attempt to gain a better grasp, today I will be trying to explain one of these ideas: the YCombinator. Info on the YCombinator is shockingly difficult to find online, as the web only seems to rank searches about VC and hackernews, but basically the YCombinator is an implementation of recursion in languages with first class functions and no recursion.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Optimization</title>
      <link>//localhost:1313/posts/2021-03-03-optimization/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 03 Mar 2021 00:00:00 +0800</pubDate>
      <guid>//localhost:1313/posts/2021-03-03-optimization/</guid>
      <description>As a kid, I remember my ambitious dreams of being an astronaut. I would carry my favorite space book everywhere with me, getting lost in the pictures of galaxies and nebulae, going to sleep under the glow in the dark stars pasted on my ceiling, dreaming of exploring. I can’t really remember a distinct time when my dream faded, though. One day, the adhesive wore off, as the stars dropped from the ceiling, lost for eternity under my bed or behind bookshelves, and I never noticed.</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
